(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
マリン船長の番組
Captain Marine's Show
マリンの劇場 2周年記念ドラマ
Marine's Theater: 2nd Anniversary Drama
#マリン船長の番組 Captain Marine's Show
#Captain Marine's Show
昼ドラホロライブ
Hololive soap opera
一夜限りと飛び込んだ
I dove in for just one night
古い旅館の2号室
To room number two of an old inn
燃ゆる花火に照らされて
Illuminated by the burning fireworks
睦言交わす熱帯夜
Whispering sweet nothings on a tropical night
朝が来るまで側にいて
Stay by my side until morning comes
あの人のこと忘れたい
I want to forget about that person
真夏の夜の泣き虫は
The crybaby of the midsummer night
声を殺して鳴くのです
Cries while stifling their voice
好きだから身を引くの
I'm stepping back because I love you
ささくれた美談丁度良い女って
A frayed beautiful story, a 'just right' kind of woman
こういうことなの？
Is this what it means?
愛してる 愛してる 愛してる 愛してる
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
幸せ探して三千里
Searching for happiness across three thousand leagues
シャラララ
Sha-la-la-la
触れ合えど 触れ合えど 触れ合えど 触れ合えど
Though we touch, though we touch, though we touch, though we touch
彷徨う運命が また恋に狂わせる
Wandering fate drives me crazy in love again
第一話
Episode 1
劣情の果て 曼交き出航
Sailing away with the after-effects of lustful emotions
お〜、あともう少しで出来るはずだにぇ。
Oh, it should be done in just a bit.
こうしてぇ…ああしてぇ…これをやってぇ…！
Like this... like that... do this...!
うわあああ！
Whoa!
これはああ！
This is...!
ついに完成したにぇ…！
It's finally complete...!
これが出回ればとんでもないことになるでぇ…あははは！
Once this gets out, it's going to be a disaster... ahahaha!
みこ部長〜❤️
Miko-bucho~ ❤️
おつかれサマンサ
Thanks for the hard work, Samantha.
やあマリンたん、今日も若作りしてるねぇ〜
Hi Marine-tan, you're trying to look young again today, aren't you?
は？
Huh?
キミもこんな時間まで仕事だったのかにぇ？
Were you working until this late too?
あの娘さんが心配してるんじゃないかな？
I bet your daughter is worried.
あ、あくあなら平気ですよっ
Oh, Aqua will be fine.
それよりぃ…
More importantly...
このあとどこか飲みに行きません〜？？
Want to go for a drink after this?
おぉいいにぇ…あの、ちょうど行ってみたいバーがあるんだよ
Oh, that sounds good... Actually, there's a bar I've been wanting to try.
『休憩所』も…すぐそばにあるんだよね…
There's also a 'rest area' right nearby...
いやんっ
Nooo!
部長のエッチ〜！
Manager, you pervert!
もう 何考えてるんですかっ
Seriously, what are you thinking?
ヘンタイ！
Pervert!
はぁわからせられる！
Ha, I'm being taught a lesson!
マリンまたわからせられちゃう〜！！
Marine is being taught a lesson again~!!
マリンたんとは行かないんだけどね
But I'm not going with you, Marine-tan.
なんで？
Why?
今日はこのあと あの 他の部署との飲み会があってねぇ
After this, well, I have a drinking session
with another department.
へぇ〜！そうなんですね！
Oh! Is that so!
マリンは聞いてないですけど なんでですか？
Marine hasn't heard about this, but why?
あ、あの あの あれだよ みんながあのほら…
Ah, well, you see... it's not like everyone...
行くわけじゃなくて 数人で行くやつだから… あのね
...is going. It's just a few people going together.
なるほどぉ〜
I see~
付き合いみたいなぁ
Like a social gathering.
じゃあマリンも行っていいですよね？
Then it's okay for Marine to go too, right?
ダメだにぇ
No way.
なんで？
Why?
あの あれなんだよ 男の… 男がいっぱいいるからね
Well, you see... there are many men there.
むさ苦しい所に マリンたんが… ねぇ 女の子で みんな興奮しちゃうからね
In such a stuffy place, Marine-tan...
as a girl, everyone will get excited.
はっ！
Ha!
たしかに マリン狙われちゃう！！！
True, Marine will be targeted!!!
暑苦しい男の人たちに囲まれて… 飲み会の主役になっちゃう…！！
Surrounded by stuffy men...
I'll become the star of the drinking session...!!
じゃあ行きますか
Well then, shall we go?
絶対ダメだにぇ ここ… 今回は 今回はね
Absolutely not. This... this time, this time, okay?
女か？
Is it a woman?
先月隣の部署に来た あの若い女か？
Is it that young woman who joined
the next department last month?
ピチピチのぉ
A youthful one?
いや ちがうねぇえ〜！！ 仕事のミーティングも兼ねてるから
No, you're wrong!! It's also for a work meeting.
他の人が来ると 困るんだよね！！ 本当にやめてもらっていいかな
So it would be a problem if other people came!!
Could you please stop?
なんだぁ そういうことですかぁ〜！
Oh, so that's how it is~!
じゃあ あの若い女はいないんですね？？
Then that young woman won't be there, right??
まあ そういうことだからね 今日は無理なんでぇ
Well, that's why, it's impossible today.
ごめんねぇマリンちゃん 本当に。 君ももうそろそろ帰りなさい 娘さんもいるしね
Sorry, Marine-chan, really. You should go home
soon too, since you have a daughter.
それじゃあ！
Well then!
やだぁ！部長！！
No way! Manager!!
若い女に乗り換えないで！！
Don't switch to a young woman!!
ちょっと… 離しなさい！
Wait... let go!
いったい
Ouch
いつになったら結婚してくれるのぉ！？
When will you marry me!?
ちょっとやめなさい君！
Wait, stop that!
待ってるのにい！！
I've been waiting!!
ここは会社なんだから！！ 一応会社なんだよ君 ここ！！
This is an office!!
It's technically an office, you!!
ひどい…
How cruel...
こんなにピチピチで 可愛くてエッチな女の子が待ってるのに
Even though such a youthful, cute,
and sexy girl is waiting
この気持ちに応えてくれないなんて
for you to not respond to these feelings...
ピチピチではないにぇ
You're not youthful.
結婚しろよぉぉ！！
Marry me!!
お、落ち着きたまえマリンちゃん！
C-Calm down, Marine-chan!
じゃあ明日結婚する？
Then, shall we marry tomorrow?
う〜ん まぁそれは早すぎるかな
Hmm, well, that's probably too soon.
じゃあいつ結婚してくれるの？？
Then when will you marry me??
まぁ あのぉ 色々手続きとかね あの 親への報告とかね…
Well, you know... there are various procedures,
informing the parents...
なんやかんや そういうのがあるから 君ももうね 娘さんもいるしね
...all sorts of things like that, and you
already have a daughter too.
そうなんだぁ…
I see...
あっ！じゃあマリンが先に部長のご両親にご挨拶に伺いましょっか！
Ah! Then should Marine go and greet
the manager's parents first!
やめて欲しいにぇ！！
I want you to stop!!
ごめんねぇマリンちゃん 君のこと 可愛くて エッチだとは思ってるけどー
Sorry, Marine-chan. I think you're cute
and sexy, but—
えぇっ// ピチピチで可愛くてエッチだなんて そんなぁ〜//
Eh// Youthful, cute, and sexy?
Oh, stop it~//
ピチピチではないにぇ
You're not youthful.
可愛くてエッチだとはおもってるけど…
I think you're cute and sexy, but...
それ以上の感情はないにぇぇ！！
I have no feelings beyond that!!
正直もうキツいにぇぇぇ！！
Honestly, it's already getting tough!!
どるるるぅぅぅああああ！！
Dorururuuuuaaaa!!
いたいけなマリンを騙しやがってよね！！
You deceived the innocent Marine, didn't you!!
許すまじっ
Unforgivable
ぜってぇ許すまじぃぃッ！！
I'll never forgive you!!
待てコラァァァァ！！！！
Wait, hey!!!!
（むせび泣く音）
(Sobbing sounds)
ひどいっ
So cruel
なんでみんなマリンを裏切りるの…
Why does everyone betray Marine...
マリンちゃん こんなに尽くしてるのに…
Even though Marine-chan is being so devoted...
これは… みこ部長の研究してる よくわからない薬… こんなものぉ！！
This is... that mysterious medicine Manager Miko
is researching... Something like this!!
あくあは… 娘のあくあは あんなに言い寄られるのに…
Aqua... even though my daughter Aqua
is being approached like that...
マリンの方がぜったいエッチなのに…
Even though Marine is definitely sexier...
どうしてっ…！
Why...!
あてぃし 恋愛とかまだ分からなくて… だからごめんなさい…！
I don't really understand love yet...
so I'm sorry...!
はぁ… 今日だけでもう45人目
Sigh... that's the 45th person just today.
いい加減 断るのも疲れちゃったなぁ
I'm getting tired of rejecting people.
あてぃし あくあ！ どこにでもいる平凡な女子高生！
I'm Aqua! Just your ordinary high school girl!
—のはずなんだけど… 毎日二ケタの男子から告白されちゃってもう大変！
—or at least I'm supposed to be... but it's tough
being confessed to by dozens of boys every day!
昨日なんか通りすがりの石油王にまで告白されて もうびっくりしちゃった！
Yesterday, I was even confessed to by a passing
oil tycoon, I was so surprised!
ただ普通に高校生活を送りたいだけなのに どうしていつもこうなっちゃうのぉ？？
I just want to have a normal high school life,
so why does this always happen??
ほかにカワイイ女の子なんかいっぱいいるのに みんなどうしてあたしなんだろう…
There are plenty of other cute girls,
so why is everyone after me...
困っちゃうなぁ
It's so troubling.
でもいつか ママが読んでくれた絵本に出てくる王子様みたいな…
But one day, like a prince from the picture books
my mom read to me...
下を向いて10回クルクル回ったあとに
A prince who can spin around 10 times
looking down...
すぐ片足立ちをしてもよろけずに
...then immediately stand on one leg
without wobbling...
愛を叫ぶことができる王子様
...and shout his love.
みたいな人が現れたら… あたしも恋に落ちるんだろうなぁ…
If someone like that appears...
I'm sure I'll fall in love too...
誰かいるわっ
Someone's there.
おい勘弁してくれよ
Hey, give me a break.
オマエみたいな女 この俺サマにふさわしいわけないだろ？
A girl like you couldn't possibly be worthy
of me, could she?
まぁ その程度のスペックで 俺サマに愛を告げた蛮勇だけは認めてやるよ
Well, I'll at least acknowledge the reckless courage
you had to confess your love to me with those specs.
俺とアベックになりたいなら わずかな期待を抱いて来世にでも賭けるんだな
If you want to be a couple with me, hold on to
a slim hope and bet on your next life.
アディオス
Adios.
おいそこに隠れてる女！
Hey, you woman hiding there!
俺サマを視界に入れる権利を奪われたくなかったら、いますぐ出てこい。
If you don't want to lose the right to keep me in your sight, come out right now.
見つかっちゃった…！
I've been found...!
ご、ごめんなさい。
I-I'm sorry.
盗み聞きするつもりじゃなかったんだけど…
I didn't mean to eavesdrop, but...
はっ！！ お驚いたぜ。
Ha! I'm surprised.
この俺サマの目を奪う女が、この世に存在するなんてな…！
To think a woman who can capture my gaze exists in this world...!
オマエ、名前はなんだ？
You, what's your name?
あくあだけど…
It's Aqua, but...
あくあか…
Aqua, huh...
この俺サマの目を一瞬でも奪った偉業に敬意を表し…
In honor of the feat of capturing my gaze, even for a moment...
俺サマのオンナにしてやるッ！！
I'll make you mine!!
え…？
Eh...?
ごめんなさい。あていしそういうの興味ないから…
I'm sorry. I'm not interested in that kind of thing...
な、なな、なんだと！？
Wh-What?!
正気か！？
Are you serious?!
それじゃあ、さよなら！！
Well then, goodbye!!
待て！
Wait!
オマエー
You...
おもしれえ女だな。
You're an interesting woman.
じゃあ… 下を向いて10回クルクル回ったあと すぐに片足立ちして
Well... try spinning around 10 times looking down, then standing on one leg
よろけずに愛を叫ぶことができるのかやってみて！
and shouting your love without stumbling!
1、2、3、4、5、6、7、8、9、10……
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10...
愛してるぜ あくあ！！
I love you, Aqua!!
俺のオンナになれッ！！
Be my woman!!
すごい…！
Amazing...!
全然できてないのにどうしてそんな自信満々なの！？
Even though you couldn't do it at all, why are you so confident!?
あなたがあていしの王子様なのね！！
You're my prince!!
好き！！
I love you!!
気づくのが遅すぎるぜ…
You're too late to realize...
シィ～オン～❤️
Shi-on~❤️
あくあ～❤️
Aqua~❤️
はぁ… 忘れようと思えば思うほど、みこ部長のことを思い出してしまうわ…
Ha... the more I try to forget, the more I remember Miko-buchou...
いまごろあの人は、あの若い女とどこかに出かけているのかしら…
I wonder if that person is out with that young woman right now...
なんだかそう思ったら、修羅場欲求がどんどん湧きたって来るッ！！
When I think about that, my desire for a scene of conflict keeps welling up!!
修羅場起こしたいッ！！
I want to cause a scene!!
アイツらの良好な関係に、クソでかに亀裂走らせたい！！
In their good relationship... I want to cause a huge rift!!
よし、修羅場起こしてこよぉ～っと！！ そうと決まったら居ても立っても居られなくなってきちゃったわ～！
Alright, I'm going to cause a scene! Now that I've decided, I can't stay still!
あっ…
Ah...
はぁ～い！ 今行きま～す！
Yes~! I'm coming~!
こんなときに一体誰よぉ～
Who could it be at a time like this?
お、お母さん…！
M-Mom...!
あの、この人、あたしの彼氏なの…！
Um, this person is my boyfriend...!
どうも。義理の母と書いて『お義母さん』。俺サマはあくあの男、シオンです。
Nice to meet you. Mother-in-law, or as I'll call you, 'Mother'. I am Shion, Aqua's man.
絶世の美男子 紫咲シオン / イイ男に目がない30代パンジョ 宝鐘マリン
The World's Most Handsome Man: Murasaki Shion / A 30s Woman with an Eye for Hunks: Houshou Marine
お母さん…？ どうしたの？
Mom...? What's wrong?
あっ… なんでもないわぁ～！
Ah... it's nothing~!
シオンくん、よくいらっしゃったわね。
Shion-kun, welcome.
狭いところだけどどうぞ。あがってあがって…！
It's a bit small, but please come in!
お母さん！ あたし自分の部屋 掃除してくるから、それまでリビングでお茶でも出しといてくれる？
Mom! I'm going to clean my room, so can you serve some tea in the living room while I'm at it?
え、ええ、もちろんよ～！
Ah, yes, of course~!
もぉ～、全く！ だからいつもお掃除しておきなさいって言ってるのに、もう！
Geez, honestly! I told you to keep it clean, but look at you!
しょうがないでしょう！ さっき来るって決まったんだもん！
I couldn't help it! It was just decided that he'd come!
それじゃあシオン、ちょっとまっててね！
Well then, Shion, wait a bit!
あぁ、そうするぜ。
Ah, will do.
どうぞ、ごゆっくり…
Please make yourself comfortable...
ごめんなさいねぇ。あの娘ったら、ほんとだらしなくて…
I'm sorry. That girl is really sloppy...
はは、大丈夫ですよ。そういうところも、ほっとけなくて可愛いですからね。
Haha, it's okay. Even that part is cute because you can't leave her alone.
ええぇ、そうね…！
Yes, that's right...!
（本当に… そういう所よね…ッ）
(Really... that's just the kind of thing she would say...)
どうしました？
What's wrong?
いえっ、なんでもないわ！ すぐにお茶をお出しするから、くつろいで待ってて。
Nothing! I'll bring some tea soon, so please relax and wait.
はいどうぞ。あ、この子ね、おかゆって言うの。シオンくん、ネコ大丈夫かしらぁ？
Here you go. Ah, this child is Okayu. Shion-kun, are you okay with cats?
もちろん平気ですよ。あくあから聞いています。何でも食べるネコ、飼ってるって。
Of course I'm fine. I heard from Aqua that you have a cat that eats anything.
そうなのよ～！ 本当、この子ったら何でも食べるから、困っちゃうわぁ。もうね。
That's right~! Honestly, this child eats anything, so it's a problem!
俺サマも、美味いもんならなんだって食べるぜ…？
I'll eat anything if it's delicious too...?
な、なっ、なんのことかしらっ… おもしろい子ね、シオンくんったら。
Oh my... whatever do you mean...? You're an interesting one, Shion-kun!
あくあから聞きましたよ。これまでお一人で、彼女を育てられたそうですね。
I heard from Aqua. You've raised her alone until now, haven't you?
大変だったでしょう？
It must have been hard?
まあそうねぇ… 大変だったけど、元気に育ってくれて嬉しいわぁ。
Well, yes... it was hard, but I'm happy she grew up healthy.
こ、こんなイケメンで… しっかりした彼氏まで連れてきてくれちゃって、母親冥利に尽きるというか何というか…
I'm so glad she brought home such a handsome and reliable boyfriend... I couldn't be happier as a mother.
でもおかしいですねぇ。お義母さんほどお綺麗なら、相手の一人や二人、すぐに見つかる気がしますけど。
But it's strange. If a mother is as beautiful as you, I'd think you'd find a partner or two in no time.
おだてたってなにも出ないわよ～。
Flattery will get you nowhere~!
お義母さん… お名前は？
Mother... what's your name?
ど、ど、どうしたの急に… マ、マリンよ。
Wh-Why so sudden... It's Marine.
そうか… マリンさん、いい名前だ。
I see... Marine-san. It's a good name.
そ、そうかしら～、どうもありがとう…
Really~? Thank you...
俺サマにはわかる… あんたはいま恋心を踏みにじられ、自分を見失っている。
I can tell... Your heart has been trampled on, and you've lost yourself.
俺サマなら、あんたの心にあいた穴を埋めてやれる。
If it's me, I can fill the hole in your heart.
俺サマだけが、マリンという海を渡る、一隻の船になれる…！
Only I can become the ship that crosses the sea called Marine...!
な、なな、何を言ってるの…！
Wh-What are you saying...!
そんな… あくあを裏切るようなこと、できるわけが…
To do something like betray Aqua... there's no way...
これまでたった一人で耐えてきたんだろ…？ 少しくらい、良い思いをしてもいいんじゃないか…？
You've endured it all alone until now... Don't you think you deserve to feel good for once?
そうよ… マリンはいっぱいがんばってきたんだもの… あくあのために、すべて犠牲にして…
That's right... Marine has worked so hard. Sacrificing everything for Aqua...
すべてではないけど…
Well, not everything...
盛った
Exaggerated
マリンだってまだチヤホヤされたい…！
Marine also still wants to be pampered...!
若くて良い男にチヤホヤされたい！！
I want to be pampered by a young, handsome man!!
脱ぎ捨てちまえ、マリン。
Strip it off, Marine.
取り繕った
Along with that mask
「優しい母親」の仮面ごと…
of a "gentle mother" you put on...
俺サマの前にすべてさらけ出せ…！
Expose everything before me...!
シオンくん…
Shion-kun...
いいえ、シオンッ！
No, Shion!
もう待ちきれない！！
I can't wait anymore!!
マリン待ちきれない！！
Marine can't wait!!
マリン…
Marine...
海と船、どっちが欠けても出来ないようなことをしようぜ…
Let's do something that can't be done if either the sea or the ship is missing...
それって、まさか！
Could it be...!
あぁ、そのまさかだ…
Yeah, exactly that...
出航
Set Sail
出航！！
Set sail!!
シオン～！
Shion~!
部屋片付け終わったから来ても大丈夫…
I've finished tidying the room, so you can come over...
シオンッ！シオン～！！
Shion! Shion~!!
あぁッ！それをそんなッ！！
Ah! You're doing that... like that!!
そんなものをこんなにしたらッ！！
If you do that to something like that!!
マリンのバミューダトライアングルがぁ！！
Marine's Bermuda Triangle is...!!
お母さん…？
Mom...?
はッ！！
Hah!!
お母さん…シオン…
Mom... Shion...
なにしてるの…？
What are you doing...?
後編へ続く
To be continued in the second half
マリン船長の番組
Captain Marine's Show
マリン船長の番組！！
Captain Marine's Show!!
はい、というわけで！！
Yes, so!!
宝鐘マリン、活動2周年、ありがとうございます！
Houshou Marine, 2nd anniversary of activities, thank you very much!
今回はですね、ちょっと趣を変えてみまして…
This time, I've changed things up a bit...
これから4コーナーあります。
There will be four segments from now on.
すでに地獄の1コーナー目をお見せしたあとなんですけども、
I've already shown you the hellish first segment, but...
ここからね、4コーナーありまして、
from here, there are four segments,
ちょっと普段の生放送ではできないような、ちょっといろんな編集を入れた、
and it's a program-style project with various edits that I can't do in a normal live stream,
なんか番組仕立ての、ちょっと企画詰め合わせみたいな感じになっているので、
it's like a collection of segments put together in a show format,
皆さんがね、笑顔になってくれたら嬉しいなと思っております。
so I hope it makes everyone smile.
番組終了後に告知もあるので、最後までチェック！！
There's also an announcement after the show, so check it out until the end!!
ちょっと結構マリンの中で重大な告知もありますので、
There's a quite important announcement from Marine too,
最後までね、しっかり見てください。
so please watch carefully until the end.
はい、このね、前半にみてもらった…
Yes, the drama you saw in the first half...
ドラマの続きねｗ
the continuation of the drama (lol)
誰も続き観たくないかもしれませんがｗ
No one might want to see the continuation (lol)
ちゃんと最後の方に続きがあるんで、
but there's a continuation at the very end,
最後の結末をお楽しみには～！！
so look forward to the finale~!!
それでは～、次のコーナーへ！！
Now then, on to the next segment!!
出航～！！
Set sail~!!
いらっしゃいませぇ！！
Welcome!!
マリンのラーメン屋さんへ、ようこそぉ～！！
Welcome to Marine's Ramen Shop~!!
はい、というわけで今日はね、ラーメン屋さんをね、
Yes, so today, I'm opening a ramen shop...
本日開店！！
Opening today!!
今日ね、開店します。バイトのメスガキです。
Opening today. Here's my bratty part-timer.
はい、バイトのメスガキもいます。
Yes, there's a bratty part-timer too.
ラーメン屋マリン
Ramenya Marine
はい、それじゃ早速ね、ちょっとまだ全然よくわかってないけど、
Alright, let's get started right away, though I don't quite understand it yet,
いきなり5分チャレ…
suddenly the 5-minute chall...
お、ビールもあるね。
Oh, there's beer too.
5分チャレンジやっていきましょう。
Let's do the 5-minute challenge.
壱回戦目
1st Round
さあ、あぁ！！応援してる！！メスガキが！！
Now, ah!! She's cheering!! The bratty girl!!
お前働けぇ！！
You, get to work!!
あ、よしよしよし。
Ah, alright, alright.
はいはいはい、ラーメンをね、作りますと。
Yes, yes, making ramen.
これはもうフィーリングでね、フィーリングで察しがつく。
I can figure this out by feel, just by feel.
はい、こう…あッ、こうして、
Yes, like... ah, do this,
えー、海苔に…こうで。
uh, seaweed... like this.
はい、どうぞ！！はい！！決まった！！
Yes, here you go!! Yes!! Perfect!!
あーっとと！！待ってマズい！！
Oops!! Wait, this is bad!!
いらっしゃい！！
Welcome!!
お、これで！！
Oh, with this!!
あ、なんか、ヤバい！！敵が来た！！敵が！！
Ah, something's bad!! An enemy came!! An enemy!!
ちょ、マズい、マズい！！
Wait, bad, bad!!
ま、招き猫アタック！！
Ma- Maneki-neko attack!!
にゃー！！よし決まった。
Nyaa!! Alright, it hit.
決まった招き猫アタック。
The Maneki-neko attack hit.
今、えーっと、忙しいな！！
Now, uh, I'm busy!!
でもね、まあ皆さんね、ご存知の通りね、マリンは…
But well, as you all know, Marine is...
なんすか、え、怒ってる！？
What the, eh, is he angry!?
なのサラリーマン！？短気なサラリーマンだなぁ、ちょっと。
That salaryman!? What an impatient salaryman, seriously.
え、また来たか！？ちょ、待って待って。
Eh, here they come again!? Wait, wait.
招き猫アタック！！
Maneki-neko attack!!
な、ロボット来た、ロボット！！
Wha-, a robot came, a robot!!
な、怒らないで！！今できた、今できた。
Hey, don't get angry!! It's ready now, it's ready now.
あ、今できたのに…
Ah, it was just ready...
これちょっともったいない、俺食べる！？
This is a waste, should I eat it!?
これもったいないから、はい…
Since it's a waste, yes...
あ、待って、お前これ、これこれ！！
Ah, wait, you, this, this, this!!
ちょ、待って、なんか来てる来てる！！
Wait, something's coming, coming!!
うりゃー！！
Uryaaa!!
待って！！もう疲れたんだけど！！
Wait!! I'm already tired!!
えーっと、あー！！
Uh, ah!!
待って、待って、待ってヤバいヤバい、焦げてる焦げてる！！
Wait, wait, wait, bad, bad, it's burning, it's burning!!
あ、できた。
Ah, it's done.
いらっしゃいませ！！
Welcome!!
ねぇ、まじで！？今！！
Hey, seriously!? Just now!!
できたじゃん、今！！
It was just done!!
何、この、短気なデブだなぁ、おいおい。
What is this, such an impatient fat guy, jeez.
あー、強盗！！強盗来た！！
Ah, robber!! A robber came!!
強盗、えーっと…
Robber, uh...
胡椒アタック！！
Pepper attack!!
あ、胡椒効かない。
Ah, the pepper doesn't work.
フライパンアタック！！
Frying pan attack!!
よし、ナイス！！えーっと…
Alright, nice!! Uh...
フライパンなくなっちゃったよ！？
The frying pan is gone!?
待って、しかもこいつじゃないし。
Wait, and it's not him.
こっちだ。はい。
It's this guy. Yes.
あんなんでもサマになって…
Even that looks good on me...
来ただろう。
It came, right?
ラーメン、ハードだな、ラーメン屋って。
Ramen... running a ramen shop is hard.
でもさ、でも確かに船長は今ね、
But, but the Captain is now,
このメスガ…
this brat...
お、あ！！ありがとう！！
Oh, ah!! Thank you!!
飲むわ、置いとこ。
I'll drink it, let's put it down.
なんだこの店のロボット率！？
What's with the ratio of robots in this shop!?
客が全員ロボット！！
The customers are all robots!!
あ、待って、なくなってる。
Ah, wait, it's gone.
ロボだし、いいか、ロボだし。
They're robots, so it's fine, since they're robots.
あ、終わった。
Ah, it's over.
はい、というわけでね、
Yes, so,
謎の1回戦目が終わったところで、ちょっとね、いろいろと反省点に気づきましたので、
now that the mysterious first round is over, I've noticed a few points to reflect on,
それをね、完全に直して、完璧なね、ラーメン屋をやっていこうなッ！！
so I'm going to fix those completely and run a perfect ramen shop!!
おー！！
Oh!!
というわけで、じゃあ、5分チャレンジ行きます。
So then, let's go for the 5-minute challenge.
弐回戦目
2nd Round
はい、まずね、なんと言ってもビールを冷やすよ、ビール。
Yes, first of all, I'll chill the beer, the beer.
ビールをね、あ、なんだ！？離れない！！
The beer... ah, what!? It won't let go!!
このビールが離れない！！
This beer won't let go!!
おい、離れろ！！あ、よし。
Hey, let go!! Ah, okay.
はい、冷やしとく。
Yes, I'll keep them chilled.
まあ6本冷やしとけば…
Well, if I chill six bottles...
壱、弐、参、四、伍…
One, two, three, four, five...
よし、はい！はい！はい！
Alright, yes! Yes! Yes!
６個。えー、えーと。
Six pieces. Uh, let's see.
この隙に、この隙に汁を入れて...
While I have a moment, I'll put in the broth...
待って、待って！できてる、できてる...
Wait, wait! It's done, it's done...
あ、待って、マァァァァァ！！！！
Ah, wait, MAAAAA!!!!
あぁぁ！！あぁぁ！！
Aaaah!! Aaaah!!
あ！二個！んで...
Ah! Two pieces! And then...
シュシュシュシュッてして...
Swish, swish, swish...
はい。あぁぁ！あぁぁ！
Yes. Aaaah! Aaaah!
できたのに！
It was ready!
あ！どっか飛んだ！待って！
Ah! It flew away! Wait!
※なぜか空を飛ぶギョウザ
*Gyoza flying through the air for some reason
ねえ、なんで！？ねえ、なんで！？
Hey, why!? Hey, why!?
ちょっと待って、えーと。待って、落ち着いて、落ち着いて。
Wait a sec, uh. Wait, calm down, calm down.
正気を取り戻して！
Regain your sanity!
ここから。ここから気を取り直していこう。
From here. Let's start fresh from here.
気を取り直して行こう
Let's start fresh
ここから。
From here.
お、冷えてる冷えてる。
Oh, it's cold, it's cold.
バッチリ冷えてますよ！
It's perfectly chilled!
はい、どうぞ！
Here you go!
えーと。
Let's see.
ちょっとここまでミスっちゃったけど...
I've made some mistakes up to this point...
ここから気を取り直して。完璧にね！
But starting now, I'll be perfect!
え、海苔。やっぱ海苔はマストだな。
Uh, nori. Nori is definitely a must.
やっぱ海苔は絶対、絶対に食べるくさい。
It seems people absolutely eat nori.
だから海苔はもう脳死で海苔を入れる。
So I'll just brainlessly put nori in.
んで、卵。はい。うぅぅぅ。
And an egg. Yes. Ugh.
なーんだ。来たか。はい！
What? Here they come? Yes!
ナイス！あ、バッチリ冷えてる。はい、はい。
Nice! Ah, perfectly chilled. Yes, yes.
ちょっと減ってきた。いつ補充する？
It's getting low. When should I restock?
はい。あ、ちょっとこぼしたけど大丈夫。
Yes. Ah, spilled a bit, but it's okay.
えーと。んで、麺入れて。麺入れて。
Let's see. Put the noodles in. Noodles in.
あ！落っこちちゃった！
Ah! It dropped!
怒っちゃった...！
He got angry...!
あぁ！なんでロボットって気が短けえな！
Ah! Why do robots have such short tempers!
気が短いな...
Short-tempered...
ラーメン食ってんじゃねえよ、ロボットが。
Don't you be eating ramen, you robot.
えーと。よいしょ。また来た。
Let's see. Up we go. Here's another one.
えーと。えい！ナイス！
Let's see. Take that! Nice!
はい、これで。麺も入れて。はい、できましたと。
Yes, with this. Noodles in too. Yes, it's done.
あ、ビール、ビール。はい、バッチバッチ。
Ah, beer, beer. Yes, chilled, chilled.
客が少ないうちに...お前もか！お前もか！
While there aren't many customers... You too!? You too!?
ちょっと減ってきた。まず、減ってきた。ビールが。
It's getting low. First, it's getting low. The beer.
これ、補充しとこう。補充。おい、おい目つき悪！お前が補充しろよ、おい！
I'll restock this. Restock. Hey, hey, what a glare! You restock it, hey!
お前が
You...
お、おぉ、ありがとう。サンキュー！サンキューな！
Oh, oh, thank you. Thank you! Thank you!
サンキュー。マジサンキュー。あ、待って。
Thank you. Seriously, thank you. Ah, wait.
汁入れて。はい、はい、はい。
Put in the broth. Yes, yes, yes.
えーと、海苔、卵、卵。はい。えー、待って、待って。
Let's see, nori, egg, egg. Yes. Uh, wait, wait.
これ、女の人と、おじさんどっちが先だ？
Which one's first, the lady or the old man?
海苔、メンマ、またか！はい、はい。はい！
Nori, bamboo shoots, again!? Yes, yes. Yes!
処理早い、処理早いぞ。慣れてきた、慣れてきた。
Fast processing, fast processing! I'm getting the hang of it!
処理早いw
Fast processing lol
処理早いぞw
Fast processing! lol
えい！これで。こんなに、やっぱ初日だから狙われてんのかな。
Take that! There. Opening day, so I guess people are out for me.
はい、卵。はい。ない！あった！はい。
Yes, egg. Yes. Not here! There it is! Yes.
うまくねーか、ちょっと。覚醒してきた。ラーメン屋で勤めるまで...
Am I not pretty good? I've awakened. Until I work at a ramen shop...
はい、メスガキエナジードリンク。はい、はい、こうで。
Yes, mesugaki energy drink. Yes, yes, like this.
はい。はい。すごい、見事なバーコード。
Yes. Yes. Wow, an impressive barcode.
見事なバーコード
Impressive barcode
あ、待って、あ、ビール、ビール。ビール！
Ah, wait, ah, beer, beer. Beer!
え、おじさん、ここ、飲み屋じゃないんですよ。
Uh, old man, this isn't a pub.
ねえ。ビールだけ飲みに来るってどういうことですか？
Hey. What do you mean by coming just for beer?
えーと、海苔入れて。
Let's see, put in the nori.
あ、ロボットが気が短いからロボット先に出して。
Robots have short tempers, so I'll serve the robot first.
はい。はい！チャーシュー。はい。あ、待って。
Yes. Yes! Chashu. Yes. Ah, wait.
入ってない、入ってない。はい！
It's not in, it's not in. Yes!
えい！ギリギリセーフ！
Take that! Safe just in time!
誰かギョウザ食べてくんない？余ってるんですけど。
Won't someone eat the gyoza? I have extra.
冷えちゃうよね。こうで、チャーシュー。はい、どうぞ！
They'll get cold. Like this, chashu. Here you go!
はぁ〜疲れた。手伝ってよ！ねえ、踊ってないで手伝ってよ！
Hah, I'm tired. Help me! Hey, don't just dance, help me!
手伝ってよ...
Help me...
はい、できました。受け取るの上手！
Yes, it's done. You're good at receiving!
またか！何回死ね！えーと、はい！
Again!? How many times, die! Let's see, yes!
あ、ロボット来た。ロボット、ロボット、あ、あ、麺が。麺。ロボットだし、いいか。
Ah, a robot came. Robot, robot, ah, noodles. It's a robot, so whatever.
ロボットだから食べれるやろの精神で。ロボットならね、この程度の衛生、衛生はね...
With the "it's a robot, so it can eat anything" spirit. For a robot, this level of hygiene...
大丈夫と。えーと、こうで、はい、こうで。
Is fine. Let's see, like this, yes, like this.
あ、あ、ちょっと、あ、あ、まずい、まずい。よいしょ。
Ah, ah, wait, ah, ah, this is bad, this is bad. Heave-ho.
あ、スクリーンショット撮っちゃった。スクリーンショット。あ、怒っちゃった！あ、ギョウザ。
Ah, I took a screenshot. A screenshot. Ah, he got angry! Ah, gyoza.
撮っちゃったw
I took one lol
い、よいしょ、あ、またギョウザか。待って、どうしたらいい？
Uh, heave-ho, ah, more gyoza. Wait, what should I do?
一旦とりあえず、これを完成させて。はい。
For now, I'll finish this. Yes.
あっちが先だっけ？どっちが先だっけ？に、あ、怒っちゃった！
Was that one first? Which was first? Two, ah, he got angry!
もう！あ、待って、ロボットは気が短いから早く出さないと。
Jeez! Ah, wait, robots have short tempers, so I have to serve them fast.
待って、待って！ロボット食べて！ロボット食べて、それ！
Wait, wait! Robot, eat! Robot, eat it!
ロボット食べて！はい！えい！海苔、卵、あ、セーフセーフセーフ！ナイス！
Robot, eat! Yes! Take that! Nori, egg, ah, safe, safe, safe! Nice!
はい、はい、はい！
Yes, yes, yes!
あぁぁぁぁ！だいぶ良くなったんじゃないですか！？
Aaaaaah! Wasn't that much better!?
はい、というわけでさっきの試合ね。
Yes, so, that match just now.
さっきの試合ね！
That match just now!
４５０点くらいだったんですけど。
I got about 450 points.
450点くらい
About 450 points
今からやるのが、最後の試合です。
The match I'm about to play will be the last one.
６００点以下だった場合は...
If it's under 600 points...
600点以下だった場合は
If it's under 600 points
本日開店なんですけど、閉店します。
Even though we opened today, we're closing.
閉店します。
We're closing.
そのくらいね、強い気持ちでやっていこうと思います。
That's how determined I am.
でもいくつか気づいた点があったんで、ちょっと紹介したいと思います。
But I noticed a few things, so I'd like to share them.
気づいた点があったんで
I noticed something
まずね、ギョウザ。これ大変なんだけど...
First, the gyoza. These are a pain, but...
これねさっき気づいたんだけど。これお皿に...
I noticed this earlier. If you put them on a plate...
ほら、これ皿にくっつくんだわ！これ！
Look, they stick to the plate! These do!
皿にくっつくんだわ！！
They stick to the plate!!
ほら、皿にくっつくから、こう一個ずつ移動せずに...
Since they stick, you don't have to move them one by one...
こうやってね...え？ちょ...
You can do it like this... Eh? Wait...
始まった？始まらない？
Did it start? Is it not starting?
ちょっと、え、待ってよ！
Wait, what, hold on!
待ってってば！
I said wait!
大丈夫か？
Are you okay?
この麺と、この海苔までは誰が来ても絶対一緒だから
Since the noodles and seaweed are the same no matter who comes...
ここまでやっておく！
...I'll get them ready up to this point!
えーとで、ここにこれを入れるだけで...
And then, just by putting this in here...
...はい完成！
...there, finished!
うま、うま！
Nice, nice!
ふざけんなマジ！！
You've gotta be kidding me!!
待ってもとに戻る
Wait, let me start over.
はい、というわけでさっきはちょっとモード間違えて...
Okay, so just now I accidentally picked the wrong mode...
...始めてしまったので、改めて！！
...so let's try that again!!
やり直していきたいと思います！
I'm going to start over!
さっき説明できなかったんですけど
I couldn't explain it before, but...
もう一個気づいたことがあって
I noticed something else.
このね、机のこの部分に...
On this part of the table here...
...秒数がね、残り秒数が出てるんだわ
...it shows the number of seconds remaining.
これをね活かして、あのせっかちなロボットとかに
Using this, for that impatient robot or whatever...
先に出すなどね、ちょっと工夫してね
...I'll try to be clever and serve them first.
待つやつは待たせる、みたいな感じでやっていきたいと思います！
I'll make the ones who can wait, well, wait!
というわけで、5分チャレンジ、最後の挑戦スタート！
So, here we go—the final 5-minute challenge starts now!
いくぞ！まず、まずはビールを冷やす！
Let's go! First, first I'll chill the beer!
まずはビールをとりあえず冷やしておいて...
I'll just chill the beer for now...
...何本冷やすか、とりあえずいっぱい冷やしておいて
...and I'll chill a bunch of them just in case.
はい、何かな？
Yes, what'll it be?
とりあえずもうこのラーメンは、汁、あ、あ、セーフ！
Anyway, for this ramen, the broth... oh, oh, safe!
汁、麺、海苔まではみんな一緒なので
Since the broth, noodles, and seaweed are the same for everyone...
ここまではもう脳死で作っていきたいと...
...I'm just going to bang them out on autopilot...
...ビール、ビール、ビール！
...Beer, beer, beer!
ビール2本！
Two beers!
はい、ま、ちょっと待っ、掴めない！
Yes, but, wait, I can't grab it!
お皿が邪魔で、どけ！
The plate's in the way, move it!
ビール置いて...
Put the beer down...
...またまた、スクショ撮って、そら！
...and again, take a screenshot, there!
えーと、で、ビールを、そして...
Um, and then the beer, and...
ドアが開いててもさ、あ、ドアが開いててもさ...
Even if the door's open... ah, even if the door's open...
あ、餃子、餃子。餃子来ましたよ！
Ah, gyoza, gyoza. Here's your gyoza!
3、4、5、6...
3, 4, 5, 6...
...で、ラーメンを脳死でラーメンを作って
...and I'll make the ramen on autopilot.
またか！何回来てんだお前、ふざけんな、待って！
Again?! How many times have you been here? Don't mess with me! Wait!
ギョウザが壊れる...！
The gyoza is breaking...!
待って、さっ！うい！
Wait, there! Whoops!
で、え、餃子。餃子はこうで...
And, uh, the gyoza. The gyoza goes like this...
...で、これができてます。
...and this one's ready.
はいはい、餃子間に合ったかな？
Okay, okay, did I get the gyoza in time?
食べてる食べてる、ナイス！
They're eating it, they're eating it! Nice!
うい、で、え、で、ここまで脳死。
Whoops, and, uh, and autopilot up to this point.
で、はいこれ入れて、はい...
Then, put this in, and...
...はい、出来上がり！
...there, it's done!
はい、一丁上がり！
One order ready!
はい、え、海苔と、卵。はい一丁上がり！
Okay, uh, seaweed and egg. One order ready!
餃子もやっておくか。
Might as well do the gyoza too.
3、4、5、6...
3, 4, 5, 6...
...で、え、こうして、え、こうして
...and, uh, do this, and, uh, do that.
ここまで脳死。で、もうすぐできる...
Autopilot up to here. And it's almost ready...
...あ、はい、あ、ちょっと待って...
...ah, yes, ah, wait a second...
...吸い寄せて。あれ、2個足りない！
...drawing it in. Wait, I'm missing two!
あー！あ、あと1個、まあいいや。
Ah! Ah, one more to go... oh well.
ちょっと待って、一旦、で卵。
Wait a second, for now... and an egg.
待って、化け物来てる、はい！
Wait, there's a monster coming! Take that!
で、あーギョウザが...！
And, ah, the gyoza...!
セーフ！餃子、餃子できてますよ！
Safe! The gyoza, the gyoza's ready!
いや、どこ、あ、はい、はい、はい！
Wait, where? Ah, yes, yes, yes!
あれ、マリンのギョウザ！？ねえなんで...？
Huh, Marine's gyoza!? Hey, why...?
なんで？さっき出来たのに...！！
Why? I just made them...!!
うるせえ！！出来た、はい、いらっしゃい。
Shut up!! It's done! Here you go, welcome.
あ、待って、デブ...あ、デブに先に出したかったのに...
Ah, wait, the fat guy... ah, I wanted to serve the fat guy first...
...くそ、女は待っとれ！
...damn it, lady, you wait your turn!
待って、ロボットに行く、あーデブ怒っちゃった。
Wait, I'm going to the robot—ah, the fat guy got angry.
餃子。ロボット早く作らないと怒るぞあいつ。
Gyoza. I have to make them fast for the robot or he'll get mad.
待って、麺入ってない。できた！
Wait, the noodles aren't in. There!
やばいやばい、あー！
Crap, crap, ah!
あーうまく行かない、うまく行かない！
Ah, it's not working, it's not working!
やだ、まだ閉店したくない！
No, I don't want to close yet!
うい、えーとこれ出来てる...
Whoops, um, this one's done...
...あー！待って！はいさ、こうで...
...Ah! Wait! Okay, like this and...
...よいしょ。まだ、まだ、まだ戦いたい！
...heave-ho. I still, still, still want to keep fighting!
えーと、海苔、えーとメンマ。はい、あった！
Um, seaweed, um, bamboo shoots. Yes, there they are!
あと10秒。こうで、メンマ。
10 seconds left. Like this, bamboo shoots.
よし、いいぞいいぞ！ハイペース、ハイペース！
Alright, looking good! Keep up the pace, keep up the pace!
海苔、メンマ、あ、メンマどこ行った？
Seaweed, bamboo shoots... ah, where'd the bamboo shoots go?
うい、はいどうぞ。ビールか、ビールビール！
Whoops, here you go. Beer, is it? Beer, beer!
はい、ビール、どうぞ。いいよいいよ、いいよいいよ！
Here's your beer. Nice, nice, looking good!
いい感じよ！あー！
It's going well! Ah!
あー何回来るんだお前！うい。えーと。
Ah, how many times are you coming?! Whoops. Um.
チャーシュー入れて。ロボット来たロボット。
Put in the pork. The robot's here, the robot.
ロボットはね、早く出さないとねこいつ...
For the robot, if you don't serve him fast...
...え、待って、あ、いないいないいない。
...wait, ah, he's gone, he's gone, he's gone.
いない、で、こうでこうで。
He's not there. So, like this and that.
あーうそ、うそ、うそ！
Ah, no way, no way, no way!
助けて、待って、うい。これ用意して...
Help me! Wait! Whoops. Prepare this...
...用意して。え、で、よいしょ...
...prepare it. Uh, and, heave-ho...
...あーどけ！で、こうして...
...Ah, move! And do this...
...あー！はい、こうでこうで、はいデブ。
...Ah! Yes, like this and that, here you go, fat guy.
あ、餃子、餃子あと2個、あと2個！
Ah, gyoza, gyoza! Two more, two more!
あと2個、待って、また餃子来てる...
Two more, wait, more gyoza orders...
...また餃子来てる。
...more gyoza orders coming in.
えーと、よしはい、あー、あ、あ...
Um, alright, yes, ah, ah, ah...
ふうッ
Phew...
焼けてねぇッ 焼けてないッ 焼けてないッ
It's not cooked! It's not cooked! It's not cooked!
うざいッ うざいッ うざいッ
Then... shut up, shut up, shut up!
いらないもう！！作り直す作り直す
I don't need this anymore!! I'll remake it, I'll remake it
あー怒っちゃった。
Ah, they got mad.
5、4、3、2、1...
5, 4, 3, 2, 1...
...えーとで、ラーメンが、えーと、海苔の、えー...
...um, and the ramen is... um, seaweed... uh...
...メンマ。はい、できてるできてる。
...bamboo shoots. Yes, it's ready, it's ready.
500円！
500 yen!
えーと、今何点だった？今何点？
Um, what was my score? What's my score?
500... 500... 早く！早く！
500... 500... Hurry! Hurry!
ということで...
And so...
ごめんな...
I'm sorry...
笑ってる... すがきやのロゴみたいな顔して笑って。
You're laughing... with a face like the Sugakiya logo.
ごめん。
I'm sorry.
お前を食わせて行きたかった。
I wanted to let you eat.
本日開店。ということで...
Shop's open today. So...
本日、閉店します。
We're closing shop for today.
毎度ありがとうございました〜！！
Thank you for your business!!
う... あっ...
Ugh... Ah...
ここ、ここは...？
Where... where is this?
あ〜良い夢見たのらぁ〜
Ah, I had such a good dream.
あれ？
Huh?
みこち... みこち？
Mikochi... Mikochi?
あれ、あたしたちさっきまで...
Wait, until a moment ago, we were...
さっきまで確か...
I'm sure until just now...
「赤ちゃんプレイ」に勤しんでいたはず...
We were supposed to be busy with "baby play"...
赤ちゃんプレイしてたのら、みこちも。
We were doing baby play, including Mikochi.
あ、ここはどこなのら？
Ah, where is this place?
先輩たち、起きやがれこの野郎。
Seniors, wake the hell up.
お生意気だぞぉ！
How cheeky!
ちょっと先輩に向かって！！
Hey, to your seniors?!
なんだその態度は！
What's with that attitude!
我が名はねねち。
My name is Nene-chi.
なんのめすがきな？
What kind of bratty girl?
ここは天界である。
This is the Celestial World.
天界？
Celestial World?
お前らは運動のしなすぎで死んだ。
You guys died from lack of exercise.
頭おかしいのら？
Are you crazy?
またまた、何言ってんだぁ？
Not again, what are you saying?
死んだんだよぉ！！
You're dead!!
もう叩かれても痛くないからね。ほらっ！
It doesn't hurt even if I hit you anymore. See!
本当だ！死んでるーーーー！！！！
It's true! I'm deaaaad!!!!
ほらっ！
See!
あうっ！
Ow!
本当だ！！
It's true!!
そいっ！
Take that!
痛くねぇ...
It doesn't hurt...
みんな死んでるんだ！！！
Everyone is dead!!!
え、どうしたら生き返れるの！？
Wait, how can we come back to life!?
やだやだまだまだ！！まだホロライブにいたいよぉ〜〜！！
No way, not yet!! I still want to be in Hololive!!
赤ちゃんプレイ早く続きしてぇのらぁ〜
I want to continue baby play soon...
生き返る為にはスポーツのテストを受けて...
To come back to life, you must take a sports test...
成績が1位だった者ののみ...
And only the one who ranks 1st...
ねねが連れて帰る。
Nene will take them back.
なあんだってぇ〜？
Wh-what was that?
え、じゃあ... 1位以外の人、は...？
Wait, then... what about the people other than 1st place...?
このまま死んだまま。
They stay dead.
えーーーーー！！！
Whaaaaaat!!!
ここにずぅ〜っと居てもらう！！
You'll have to stay here forever!!
いやでも待って！！この二人には負けない...
Wait! I won't lose to these two...
ねね先生おねがいしまぁ〜す！！
Nene-sensei, please help!!
あ、狡い！！負けませんよ！こんな軽やかな動き！
Ah, unfair!! I won't lose! Look at these light movements!
こんなBBAに負けてたまるか！！！
As if I'd lose to this hag!!!
誰がBBAじゃ！デコォ！！！
Who's a hag! Forehead!!!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
ついて行きます！
I'll follow you!
はっ！ここは！？
Hah! This place!?
ここはどこだ！！
Where are we!!
なんなのらここはぁ〜！
What is this place?!
ここは今からみんなに競技してもらう会場だ。
This is the venue where you'll be competing from now on.
なんだってぇ〜〜！！！
What was that?!!!
まずはね、運動不足の君たちが怪我をしないようにストレッチをしていきたいと思う！
First, I want to do some stretching so that you exercise-deprived people don't get hurt!
めんどくせぇなぁ〜
What a pain...
じゃあいきなり... 100mくらいずつ走っとこうみんな。
Then suddenly... let's all run about 100m.
やだやだ！嫌です！帰りたーい！
No way! I refuse! I want to go home!
やる気出せやる気！足りてねーな体力が！！
Show some enthusiasm! You lack stamina!!
それではまず第一競技、はい。反復横跳びを行いたいと思います！
Now for the first competition. Yes. We'll be doing repeated side jumps!
えーやだー。忘れちゃったよ。どうやって飛ぶの？
Eh, no way. I forgot. How do you jump?
ルール、1セット20秒で、この線を越えるたびに1カウントずつ増えていく感じになります。
Rule: One set is 20 seconds. Every time you cross these lines, your count increases by one.
得意なやつ来ました！！
My specialty has arrived!!
『ライン超え』！ライン超え！
Line crossing! Line crossing!
先生のお手本をまず見せて貰えますか？
Could you show us the teacher's demonstration first?
あ、お願いします。
Yes, please.
それでは、ねねちの反復横跳びまで、3, 2, 1, GO!
Now, for Nene-chi's repeated side jumps. 3, 2, 1, GO!
早い早い早い！！
Fast, fast, fast!!
すごーーーい！！！
Amaaaaazing!!!
じゃあこれをね、参考記録に。余裕だよね、みんな！帰りたいもんね？天界から。
Now, use this as a reference record. It's easy, right everyone? You want to go back, right? From the Celestial World.
帰りたい！帰りたい！
We want to go back!
おろおろ...
Flustered...
ほら、本日主役の船長！
Come on, today's protagonist, Captain!
え、できるかなぁ〜。わおー！わおー！
Eh, can I do it? Wow! Wow!
内股内股！何あいつ。
Pigeon-toed! What's with her?
じゃあ船長の反復横跳びまで、3, 2, 1, スタート！
Now, for the Captain's repeated side jumps. 3, 2, 1, START!
『横跳び』してなくねぇのら？え、何あいつ。
She's not even doing "side jumps", is she? Eh, what is she doing?
足動いてねーのら、こいつ。
Her legs aren't even moving.
ワタワタしてね？
Isn't she just flailing?
ドタバタしてる。コミカルな動きや。
She's just clattering around. What a comical movement.
これ本気... 本気なのら？え、ふざけてるのら？
Is she serious? Eh, is she messing around?
おパン○が見えちゃう！おパン○が見えちゃうよ！
Her panties are going to show! Her panties are going to show!
じゃあ船長の、え、ライン超え回数は24回かな？
So the Captain's, uh, line crossing count is 24?
盛り上がりが微妙すぎる。半端やわ。
The excitement is too subtle. It's lukewarm.
次はあーしだ！
Next is me!
次は、みこ先輩行こう！
Next, Miko-senpai, let's go!
みこ先輩、行かせていただきますよ。余裕だね。
Miko-senpai will go now. It's easy.
じゃあみこ先輩の、反復横跳びまで...
Then, for Miko-senpai's repeated side jumps...
見てろよ！生きてみせる！
Watch me! I'll come back to life!
3, 2, 1, スタート！
3, 2, 1, START!
1, 2, 3...
4, 5, 6...
12, 13, 14...
15, 16... なんか遅くない？
15, 16... isn't it slow?
17, 18, 19...
足が悲鳴をあげている...!!
My legs are screaming...!!
21, 22, 23... FINISH!
あら〜みこち!? あれ？遅くなってた？
Wait, Mikochi!? Huh? Did I get slower?
よくもイキってくれたな!! バシッ!
How dare you act so tough!! *Whack!*
痛い!! もう! よくもイキってくれたな!
Ouch!! Jeez! How dare you act so tough!
マイナス分も合わせまして、結果23回かな？
Including the deductions, the result is 23 times?
何回だった?? (船長は) 24回
How many was it?? (Captain got) 24 times.
えっ!? ああ〜っはっはっ!! マリン船長に負けてる!!
What!? Aah-hah-hah!! You lost to Captain Marine!!
フォームはみこ先輩の方が50倍くらい綺麗だった
Miko-senpai's form was like 50 times more beautiful.
何だって!!
What did you say!!
じゃあ最後ルーナ先輩。現状1位は24回の船長なんで超えてって下さい
Then finally, Luna-senpai. Currently 1st is Captain with 24, so please beat that.
どんどんパルコアライン超えていくなんなの〜
I'm going to keep crossing the parkour lines nano~
ルーナ先輩の反復横跳びまで、3, 2, 1, GO!
Until Luna-senpai's side-to-side jumps... 3, 2, 1, GO!
1, 2, 3... あら速い
1, 2, 3... Oh, she's fast.
6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12...
13, 14, 15... 22...
23, 24, 25... 32! すげー!
23, 24, 25... 32! Amazing!
33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38! FINISH!
うわああ! ルーナたん!!? ルーナたん!!
Uwaaa! Luna-tan!!? Luna-tan!!
ルーナたんがぁぁ!! シンジャッタヨォ!!
Luna-tangaaaa!! She died!!
本気出しちゃった...
I gave it my all...
まだ1回目なんだけどな競技。甘いなルーナたん
It's only the first event though. You're naive, Luna-tan.
でも結果はルーナ先輩なんと38回!
But the result for Luna-senpai is a whopping 38 times!
いえぇ〜い!!
Yee-haw!!
すごいよ! 息がすごいよぉ!
Amazing! Your breathing is intense!
さあ何とね、今日は競技がいっぱいありますので、さっそく次の競技に!!
Well, since there are many events today, let's move on to the next one!!
じゃあ次の競技このままいきたいと思いますが
Then I'd like to move on to the next event...
次はね、簡単だよみんな!
Next is easy, everyone!
次はね、バランス立ちって言って、目を閉じてどれくらい片足でバランスを保っていられるか
Next is the balance stand, where you close your eyes and see how long you can balance on one leg.
なるほどね。いけるわこれはな
I see. I can do this.
ルール：目を閉じ片足立ちをし、どれくらい長く保っていられるかを競う
Rule: Compete for how long you can hold a one-legged stand with your eyes closed.
こっち、ルーナたんこっち。え、なんで？うん、こっち
This way, Luna-tan this way. Eh, why? Yeah, over here.
絵面的にこうかなって
I thought this would look better on screen.
いくよ〜!! せーのって言ったらみんな同時に足を上げてください。3, 2, 1, GO!
Here we go~!! Everyone raise your leg together. 3, 2, 1, GO!
いやあぁぁぁぁぁぁ!!
Iyaaaaaaa!!
違う勝負してない？大丈夫？
Aren't you doing a different competition? Are you okay?
今この人が!! ルーナの妨害をしてきました!!
Just now, this person!! Interfered with Luna!!
船長がみこのこと妨害してきました!!
Captain interfered with Miko!!
私この人に妨害されました!!
I was interfered with by this person!!
手ないもぉ〜ん!!
I don't have hands!!
じゃあ行きましょうみんな。3, 2, 1, GO!
Then let's go everyone. 3, 2, 1, GO!
もうダメだよ押しちゃ
No more pushing, okay.
コアマッスルを意識して
Focus on your core muscles.
ばか!! 体幹のチェックを... ガタガタガタ!!
Stupid!! Checking the core... *rattle rattle!!*
おれおれ、いい感じだ
Oh, this feels good.
ルーナ先輩も、ガタガタガタ!!
Luna-senpai too, *rattle rattle!!*
うわあああ!! 情けないね!!
Uwaaaaaa!! How pathetic!!
ちょっと押された程度でそんなフラフラしちゃってさ!!
Getting all wobbly just from being pushed a little!!
おつおつおつ!!
RIP RIP RIP!!
ザコｗ ウゼェェ!!
Noob lol. SO ANNOYING!!
いえぇ〜い!! どうよ??
Yee-haw!! How's that??
現状は船長が1位
Currently Captain is 1st.
なにブーブーしてんのよ!
What are you booing about!
次がね、上体そらしって言って。うつ伏せの状態で寝転んで
Next is the upper body back extension. Lie down on your stomach.
ルール：うつ伏せの状態で背中を後ろに反ってあごが何センチ上がるかを競う
Rule: From there, arch your back and see how many centimeters your chin rises from the ground.
どちらかと言うと体の柔らかさと腹筋とか背筋の感じなのかな
It's probably about flexibility and core/back muscle strength.
柔らかいわよ〜マリン。上半身柔らかいよ
I'm flexible~ Marine. My upper body is flexible.
乗りたい乗りたい。乗るのみこちに。え、船長に？
I want to ride. I'll ride on Mikochi... wait, on Captain?
こっちはそんな上がらないのあり
Is it okay if I don't go up that high?
痛たた! お尻叩かないで!!
Ouch! Don't hit my butt!!
さあと言うわけで、船長の上体そらし... スタート!
Well then, Captain's upper body back extension... start!
えっ、すごいすごい！
Eh, amazing, amazing!
柔らかい！！
So flexible!!
53cm！おー、すごい！
53cm! Oh, amazing!
顔もうるさかった！
Her face was noisy too!
みこち！！
Mikochi!!
え、じゃあ今度ルーナ乗りたい！
Eh, then this time Luna wants to ride!
乗ってやるぜぇ！
I'm gonna ride ya!
やだぁ～おむつがついちゃうよぉ
Nooo, the diaper's gonna touch me!
おむつじゃねーのらぁ～！！
It's not a diaper-nora~!!
けっこう下がったw
Dropped quite a bit lol
ここだから、35cmかな？
Since it's here, is it about 35cm?
記録35cm
Record: 35cm
しょぼぉ～いｗ
Pathetic lol
ねね、乗っていいかなぁ...
Can Nene ride...?
いくのらぁ
Here I go-nora
覇気ないけど大丈夫？ｗ
No spirit, you okay? lol
10cm
はい！じゃあ結果出ましたね！
Alright! The results are in!
というわけで1位が船長で「53cm」！
So, 1st place is Captain with "53cm"!
みこ先輩の「35cm」！
Miko-senpai's "35cm"!
ダントツ最下位の「10cm」ルーナ先輩。
By far last place is "10cm", Luna-senpai.
しかし続く立ち幅跳びでは...
However, in the following standing long jump...
ルーナが圧勝！！
Luna wins by a landslide!!
あらぁ、かわいそうな人たちが...
Oh my, those poor people...
バトルロワイヤルラン！
Battle Royale Run!
さあ今からね、持久走でみんなで勝負を...
Now then, everyone's gonna compete in a distance run...
リズムに遅れないようにどれだけ走り続けられるかを競う
Compete to see how long you can keep running without falling behind the rhythm
死んでしまうわけね！
So we'll die!
簡単なのらねぇ
That's easy-nora
みこち1回も1位になれてないからなぁ～
Mikochi hasn't been 1st even once yet~
1位を取らせて頂きたいなぁと思っておりますよねぇ
I'm thinking I'd like to let me take 1st place
ムリムリw
No way lol
なんか、先生余裕だぞ！！
Teacher looks so relaxed!!
早送り
Fast forward
行かないでみんな
Don't go everyone
まったく間に合ってません
Not making it at all
みこちお前良いのかよ！！
Mikochi, are you okay with that!!
1回も1位になれないまま！！
Without being 1st even once!!
上体起こし
Sit-ups
ルーナの時代きたなこりゃ
Luna's era has come, I see
50回やってやるから見てろ
I'll do 50, just watch
30秒で50回もできるわけないじゃん！！
There's no way you can do 50 in 30 seconds!!
先生の参考記録から見ますかじゃあ
Shall we see the teacher's reference record first?
（吸引）なんかチューしてるみたい
(Suction) Looks like she's kissing
ねね！やだやだ！
Nene! No no!
やめなさい！！ずっとチューするんじゃねー
Stop it!! Stop kissing the whole time
何回か数えてた？
Were you counting how many times?
すいません、船長もチューに夢中でw
Sorry, Captain was also distracted by the kissing lol
準備いいですか？
Are you ready?
待って。もうしんどい。
Wait. I'm already tired.
行きましょう。
Let's go.
はい。数えます。
Okay. I'll count.
３、２、１、ゴー！スタート！
3, 2, 1, Go! Start!
ふんっ！いーち！
Hmph! One!
アアイアイ！！！
Aai-ai!!!
オオオイ！！！
Ooooi!!!
声の勢いやべえのらｗ
The intensity of her voice is crazy-nora. lol
声がもたないのら。
She has no voice left-nora.
フゥゥゥゥ！！！
Fuuuu!!!
近すぎ、近すぎ！
You're too close, too close!
はい！９回目、９回目！
Yes! The 9th one, 9th one!
おね！はい１０回目１０回目！
One more! Yes, the 10th one, 10th one!
３、２、１、フィニッシュ！
3, 2, 1, Finish!
はい、１０回。
Yes, 10 times.
聞いて。笑わされるからね。できなくなるから。
Listen. I can't do it because they keep making me laugh.
覚えといて。
Remember that.
３秒に１回だったね、船長ｗ
It was once every 3 seconds, Senchou. lol
うるせぇ！ｗ
Shut up! lol
じゃあ次、みこ先輩。
Next, Miko-senpai.
ルーナは本当にマジなんだよ。
Luna is really serious about this.
何回できるかな。船長の１０回を笑えるようなレベルなのかな？
I wonder how many she can do. Is she at a level where she can laugh at my 10 times?
どうなのかな、かな？
I wonder how it'll be?
うわああああああ！
Uwaaaaaaa!
３、２、１、ゴー！スタート！
3, 2, 1, Go! Start!
せーの！ふにゅぅ！
One-two! Funyuu!
上がってないよ全然！！みこち！！！
You're not getting up at all!! Mikochi!!!
ちょっとみこち！！諦めないで！もう一回、もう一回！
Wait, Mikochi!! Don't give up! One more time, one more time!
せーの！いーっつ！
One-two! Ii-tsu!
えぇ？でも頭から離れてる…
Eh? But her head is leaving the floor...
離れてる、離れてる！いいよ！落として、落として！
It's leaving, it's leaving! Good! Lower it, lower it!
ほんとに出来ないんだって！！
I really can't do it!!
せーの！いーっつ！
One-two! Ii-tsu!
毎回手こうなんのなによｗ
Why do your hands always end up like this? lol
手振られてる赤ちゃんに。ヤッホー！ヤッホー！
You're like an infant waving hands. Yahoo! Yahoo!
逃げるな！逃げるな！あと５秒、あと５秒！
Don't run away! Don't run away! 5 seconds left!
離してぇぇぇぇ！！！
Let go of meeeee!!!
この屈辱…！！
This humiliation...!!
０回！
0 times!
恥ずかしくないのみこち。
Isn't this embarrassing, Mikochi?
恥ずかしくないのこんなんでｗ恥ずかしいよ！
Isn't this embarrassing? Yes, it's embarrassing! lol
もうやだ！！
I've had enough!!
ここにずっといるよぉぉ！！
I'll stay here foreveeeeer!!
みこ先輩が転がっていく。
Miko-senpai is rolling away.
情けない結果ですけども。
What a pitiful result.
ルーナたんがね、今からね、すごい記録。２秒に１回やってくれるからね。
Now, Luna-tan will show us a great record. She'll do one every two seconds.
そこで寝てる人いるのらけど？
There's someone sleeping there-nora?
腹筋０回の人どいてください。邪魔なんですけどぉ。
Zero-sit-up person, please move. You're in the way.
ヒデぇよぉ〜（泣）
Cruel~ (crying)
はいじゃあルーナ先輩。３、２、１…ピースする余裕ありだね。ピースまで。
Alright, Luna-senpai. 3, 2, 1... She has room for a peace sign. Even for a peace sign.
３、２、１、ゴー！スタート！
3, 2, 1, Go! Start!
いーち！にー！
One! Two!
チューチュー！
Chu-chu!
よん！ごっ！ろく！なな！
Four! Five! Six! Seven!
なんか余裕がある！！
She has quite some room!!
じゅう！じゅういち！じゅうに！じゅうさん！
Ten! Eleven! Twelve! Thirteen!
じゅうよん！じゅうご！じゅうろく！じゅうなな！じゅうはち！３、２、１、フィニッシュ！
Fourteen! Fifteen! Sixteen! Seventeen! Eighteen! 3, 2, 1, Finish!
あれ、でも待って。あれ、５０回…あれルーナたん５０回は？
Wait, 50 times? Where are the 50 times, Luna-tan?
１８回。くっそー。
18 times. Dammit.
いや凄いな。あんなに笑わされても余裕で。うわ凄いな。
That was amazing, even with all that laughing. That's impressive.
仲間だと思ってたのにぃ。
I thought we were comrades...
一緒にしないで欲しいのら（笑）
I don't want to be grouped with you-nora. (lol)
ダンス！ダンスだー！
Dance! It's dance!
ダンスダンスダンス！イエーイ！
Dance-dance-dance! Yay!
みこ先輩いいね！
Miko-senpai is good!
みこ初勝利！！
Miko's first victory!!
お前腹筋０回だろ！！イキってんじゃねぇ！！
You were at zero for sit-ups though!! Don't act all high and mighty!!
結果発表！イエーイ！
Announcement of results! Yay!
さあ、たくさん競技やってきましたーが！一番１位を取れたのは、
We've done many challenges. Who took 1st place the most?
結局誰だったのか！！
Who was it in the end?!
誰なのかな、かな？
I wonder who it is?
というわけで、ねねと一緒に人間界に帰宅できるのは！？
So, the one who can return to the human world with Nene is...
ドゥルルルルルルルルル…
Drumroll...
姫森ルーナ！！
Himemori Luna!!
まあルーナよく言っていたのら。息切れは「演技」だと。
Well, Luna often said that being out of breath was "acting".
めちゃくちゃ裏でバテ散らかしてた癖に！！
Even though you were totally exhausted behind the scenes!!
イェーイ！嬉しい！
Yay! I'm happy!
じゃあルーナたん人間界へ帰ろう！
Let's go home, Luna-tan!
いっぱいお菓子用意してるよ。
I've got lots of snacks ready.
待って連れてって。
Wait, take me too.
来んじゃねぇ！！
Don't come near us!!
やだぁ、ルーナたん待ってぇ、赤ちゃんプレイしよぉ。赤ちゃんプレイよぉ！
Wait, Luna-tan! I want to play baby too! Play baby with me!
みこちずっと一緒なんだね。
We're left together, Mikochi.
当然。うちらもうずっとここで二人きりなんだ。仲良くしよう、もう。ね、みこち。
Of course. It's just the two of us here from now on. Let's get along, Marine.
みこち一緒にここで赤ちゃんプレイしよ。
Mikochi, let's play baby together here.
やだ。
No.
みこより体力ある奴と一緒に居れない！
I can't be with someone who has more physical strength than me!
んだよぉぉ！！
What was that?!
こっちだってこんなポンコツと暮らせるかよ！！！
As if I could live with such a klutz!!!
このポンコツが！！おら、お前ふざけんなよ！待て待て待て、離せ。
You klutz!! Hey, don't mess with me! Wait, wait, let go.
マリンちゃんスイッチ
Marin-chan Switch
さあ、天音かなたちゃんと一緒に、
Now, together with Amane Kanata-chan,
マリンが何のポーズをしているか当ててみてね！
try to guess what pose Marine is making!
マリンちゃんスイッチ。
Marin-chan Switch.
あ！
A!
え？これなに？スケート？
Eh? What is this? Skating?
あ、あれ？また一人でクリスマスなのに、
Oh, huh? Even though it's Christmas,
あれ？あれ一人でスケートしに行くマリン？
is Marine going skating all alone again?
あれれ？一人だぞ？
Oh? She's all by herself.
なんだこのポーズ、一人でポーズをとっているア・イ・アイドル！
What's with this pose? Taking a pose alone, i... i... idol!
あ　アイドル
A: Idol
アイドルじゃねーだろ！なんだよさっき…え、なにそのポーズ？
That's not an idol! What was that just now... eh, what's that pose?
マリンちゃんスイッチ。
Marin-chan Switch.
い！
I!
い、今度当てるぞ？
I, I'll guess it this time.
胃が痛くて…い、
My stomach hurts... I...
胃が痛すぎるまである。
It might even be that my stomach hurts too much.
胃が痛すぎるまである…
It might even be that my stomach hurts too much...
なんでこの手のモジャモジャ…
What's with this fluff on the hands...
い、いいんですか？そんな風に…
I, is it okay? To be like that...
イソギンチャク！わかるわけねーだろ、イソギンチャク！
Sea anemone! There's no way I'd know that, a sea anemone!
い　イソギンチャク
I: Sea Anemone
マリンちゃんスイッチ。
Marin-chan Switch.
う！
U!
ちょっと雲行き怪しいんだけど…
The outlook is getting a bit suspicious...
埋もれとる…あ、わかった！
She's buried... Ah, I've got it!
埋もれてる床に。埋もれたマリンも愛して…
Buried in the floor. Love the buried Marine too...
いや待ってこれ、有象無象じゃない？わかった、有象無象！
No wait, is this 'rabble'? I've got it, 'the rabble'!
有象無象、有象無象に紛れるマリン…
The rabble, Marine blending in with the rabble...
なんか撫でてきている…有象無象のマリン…
She's stroking something... The rabble Marine...
生まれたてのベイビー！惜しい！
A newborn baby! So close!
う　生まれたてのベイビー
U: Newborn Baby
わかんねーよ生まれたてのベイビー！ちょっとおかしいんだけど…
There's no way I'd know a newborn baby! This is a bit weird...
マリンちゃんスイッチ。
Marin-chan Switch.
え！
E!
えー？
Eeeh?
あー、これは…ちょっとおかしいな…
Ah, this is... it's a bit weird...
なんだこれ…え、え、まさか盆踊りが…
What's this... E, E, could it be a Bon dance...
えっちっちのよいよいよい！どういうこと！？近かった盆踊り！
Ecchi-chi-no yoi yoi yoi! What does that even mean!? The Bon dance was close!
え　えっちっちのよいよいよい
E: Ecchi-chi-no yoi yoi yoi
マリンちゃんスイッチ。
Marin-chan Switch.
お！
O!
おしりじゃないこれ？
Isn't this a butt?
おしりを見ないでくださいね。
Please don't look at my butt.
おしりを見ないでくださいマリンの…
Please don't look at Marine's butt...
お、お近いお近いこれ当たってるぞ！
O, so close, so close, I'm getting this right!
お　おしりプリプリ
O: Wiggling Butt
マリンちゃんスイッチ。
Marin-chan Switch.
ま！
Ma!
まである、そこまで対応する…
It might even be... going that far to respond...
まであるを対応しすぎている「まである」じゃないこれ？
Isn't this 'it might even be' since you're responding too much?
まざいの方か！まざいか！
Oh, it's 'Mazai'! Is it 'Mazai'?
ま　まざい(魔剤)
Ma: Mazai (Energy Drink)
まざい…まであるかと思った…
Mazai... I thought it was 'it might even be'...
疲れましたね…はぁ…
I'm exhausted... *sigh*...
もう勘弁してくれ…あぁ…
Give me a break... Aah...
ほんとちょっとカメラ引いて、カメラ引いて…もうマリンを映さないで、疲れ切った。
Seriously, zoom the camera out, zoom out... don't show Marine anymore, I'm spent.
ちょっと本当に、タオルが欲しい。完じゃねーよ！
Seriously, I want a towel. It's not the end!
昼ドラホロライブ
Hololive Soap Opera
お母さん…シオン…なにしてるの…？
Mother... Shion... what are you doing...?
ちがっ、違うのあくあッ！
No, it's not what it looks like, Aqua!
違う全然違うの、あくあ。これにはわけがあるの。
It's completely different, Aqua. There's a reason for this.
ないけどあるの、あくあ。
There isn't one, but there is, Aqua.
お母さん…あたしの彼氏に…手出したの！？
Mother... you laid a hand on... my boyfriend!?
いやぁ、マリンが俺サマを誘惑してきたからつい…
Well, Marine tempted me, so I just couldn't help it...
常習犯
Habitual Offender
黙っててシオン！！間違えた、黙ってなさいシオンくん！
Shut up, Shion!! I mean, please be quiet, Shion-kun!
最低…お母さん最低だよ！！
Terrible... Mother, you're the worst!!
浮気性のシオンはともかく、お母さんそんな人だったなんて…！！
Setting aside the cheating Shion, I can't believe you were that kind of person...!!
あたしの彼氏と「出航」するようなそんな女だったなんて！！
To think you were the kind of woman who would "set sail" with my boyfriend!!
あくあ落ち着いて、あなた誤解してるの。
Aqua, calm down, you're misunderstanding things.
あなたのお母さんがそんなことするわけないでしょう？
Your mother would never do something like that, right?
シオンくんの目にゴミが入ってたからちょっと出航しただけ。
Shion-kun just had some dust in his eye, so we "set sail" for a bit.
してない、してないわあくあ。お母さんのこと信じられるわよね？
I didn't, I didn't do it, Aqua. You can believe your mother, right?
お母さんのバカ！！
Mother, you idiot!!
オバサンのくせに若い子と出航なんかして、恥ずかしくないのぉ！？
At your age, "setting sail" with a young guy, aren't you ashamed!?
しかもわたしの彼氏となんて！！
And with my boyfriend of all people!!
オバサンのくせに、みっともない！！
For an old lady, it's pathetic!!
恥知らず！！もう裏切り者！！お母さんなんて…！！
Shameless!! You traitor!! I hate you, Mother...!!
うううううるっせええええええ！！！！
SHUT THE HELL UUUUUUP!!!!
誰がババアだこのアマ！！
Who are you calling an old hag, you bitch!!
ガキのくせに一丁前にオンナみてえなこと抜かしやがってよぉ！！
Talking like a grown woman when you're just a brat!!
ああああイライラする！！
Aaaaah, it's so irritating!!
まだそんな歳じゃないのに！！マリンちゃんイライラする！！
I'm not at that age yet!! Marine-chan is getting irritated!!
誰が今まで育ててやったと思ってんだよオイ！！
Who do you think has been raising you all this time, huh!?
娘の彼氏の一りや二人、
Having a little taste of my daughter's
つまみ食いしたってバチ当たらねえだろうがよぉ！！
boyfriend or two... there's no harm in that, right!?
※当たる
*It does.
なによ！！悪いことしたのはお母さんなんでしょう！？
What!? You're the one in the wrong, Mother!!
これ以上あたしの彼氏に手出さないで！！
Don't lay another hand on my boyfriend!!
嫌ですぅ〜〜。
No way~~~.
シオンはお母さんの彼氏ですぅ〜〜。
Shion is Mommy's boyfriend now~~~.
だいたいあんた…
Besides, you...
どうせまだ出航もしてないんでしょう〜？？
You probably haven't even set sail yet, have you??
っししし...
Heh heh heh...
してますけどぉ！？
I have though!?
うわ〜www してないんだぁ〜ww
Wow... she totally hasn't.
あれぇ〜？？お母さんはもうしましたけど〜？？
Oh? Mother has already done it, you know?
出会って即出航しましたけどぉ〜？？w
We set sail immediately after meeting!
このクソBBAアアア！！！
You shitty old hag!!!
おいふたりとも、俺サマは複数人同時に攻略出来るから心配するなよ
Hey you two, don't worry, I can handle multiple people at once.
うるさい！！シオンは黙ってて！！
Shut up!! Shion, stay out of this!!
うわっなんか落としちゃったぁ(棒)
Whoops, I dropped something. (monotone)
もぐもぐ... ぺろぺろ...
Munch munch... lick lick...
ああああ！！それはみこ部長の作った変な薬！！
Aaaah!! That's the weird potion Club President Miko made!!
おかゆ...！！おかゆだめ！！
Okayu...!! Okayu, no!!
なによそれ！！
What is that!?
おかゆ早く吐きなさい！！
Okayu, spit it out now!!
吐きなさい！！
Spit it out!!
もうそれ、ボクで良くない〜？
Isn't it fine if you just go with me now?
なんて魅力的なケモミミ美男子(美少女)！？
What a charming kemomimi handsome boy (beautiful girl)!?
おかゆがこんなに素敵なケモミミ美男子だったなんて...！！
I never knew Okayu was such a wonderful kemomimi handsome boy...!!
もうほかの男なんかどうでもいい！！！
I don't care about any other guys anymore!!!
マリン、おかゆと出航したい！！
Marine wants to set sail with Okayu!!
いいよ〜
Sure~
ダメよ！！元々おかゆはあたしが飼ってたんだから！！
No way!! I was the one who was keeping Okayu in the first place!!
おかゆはあたしのよ！！
Okayu is mine!!
そうだねぇ〜
That's true~
おいなに言ってんだっ！こんな良いケモミミオンナ、俺サマのもんに決まってるだろ！？
Hey, what are you saying!? A kemomimi girl this good obviously belongs to me!?
そうとも言えるねぇ
You could say that too~
マリンちゃん！！！
Marine-chan!!!
本当に... ごめん、悪かったにぇ！！
I'm really... sorry, I was wrong!!
本当に僕のことを愛してくれていたのは、君だけだったとー
That the only one who truly loved me was you—
あれっ、あっ！！
Huh? Ah!!
あれ〜〜！？もしかして僕の研究が... 完成していたのか！！
Wait~~!? Could it be that my research... was actually complete!?
これは... 僕が大好きなケモミミ美少女だにぇぇぇ！！
This is... the kemomimi beautiful girls that I love so much!!
うるせぇクソジジイ！！！
Shut up, you shitty old man!!!
おかゆに触ってんじゃねえ！！
Don't you dare touch Okayu!!
おにぎり買いに行ってきま〜す
I'm going to go buy some onigiri~
絶対許さないんだから！！
I'll never forgive you!!
ひどい... なんでみんなマリンを裏切るの？マリンちゃん、待ってたよ... こんなに尽くしてるのに...
Terrible... why does everyone betray Marine? Marine-chan was waiting... even though I've done so much for you...
これ、どこだ...？w
Where is this...? lol
くすりw どこだって、なに、どこだって、くすり
The medicine lol. What do you mean 'where is it', where... the medicine.
お母さん、あたし自分の部屋掃除してくるから。それまでリビングにシオンちゃんに、お茶... あ、シオンちゃんじゃないか...
Mother, I'm going to clean my room. Until then, in the living room for Shion-chan, some tea... oh, it's not Shion-chan...
あ、シオン... あ、ごめん
Ah, Shion... ah, sorry.
おかゆがこんなに素敵なケモミミ美男子だったなんて...！！
I never knew Okayu was such a wonderful kemomimi handsome boy...!!
もうほとほ...
Already alm...
なんて言った？w 略しちゃったw
What did I say? lol I abbreviated it lol
マリンちゃん！僕が、悪かったにぇ... あの...
Marine-chan! I was wrong... um...
本当に、ごめん... あにゃ... わんじゃねえわ
I'm really sorry... anya... wait that's not it.
宝鐘マリン x Yunomi コラボの電子ドラック的オリジナル楽曲。6名の白熱アニメーターさんたちのアニメミュージックビデオに乗せて、このあと22時プレミア公開！
Houshou Marine x Yunomi collaboration electronic-drug-like original song. With an anime music video by 6 hot animators, it'll have a premiere release at 22:00!
1回見ても聴いても理解できない不思議な曲です。君の頭を征服する電子ドラックになりたい。
It's a strange song that you won't understand even after watching or listening once. I want to be an electronic drug that conquers your head.
宝鐘マリン2周年グッズの告知です！まずは、こちら。キャンバスアートです。
Announcement for Houshou Marine 2nd anniversary goods! First, this. Canvas art.
見てください、この色気溢れる風貌。人目を憚らずジロジロ見るためにも、購入するしかないですね。
Look at this appearance overflowing with sexiness. To stare at it without worrying about others, you've got no choice but to buy it.
続いて、だいぶ前に君たちから提案された海賊旗をついにグッズにしてみました。
Next, I've finally made the pirate flag that you guys suggested a long time ago into merchandise.
部屋に飾ればそれだけで、そう。そこは宝鐘海賊団の船になるのだ。
If you hang it in your room, just like that, yes. It becomes a ship of the Houshou Pirates.
そして、こちら。船長がお胸につけているバッジとお揃いのネクタイピンです。
And this. A tie pin that matches the badge Captain wears on her chest.
え、ネクタイつけてないよって君も、これを部屋に置いておけば... もう、船長、忘れ物して。と、何かあった一夜を演出できますね。
Eh, for you who says 'I don't wear a tie,' if you leave this in your room... you can stage a night where 'Oh, Captain, you forgot something.'
全部セットでご購入いただきましたらば、こちらのポストカードがついてきます。ポストカード、集めてますよね？目指せ全種コンプ！
If you purchase the full set, you'll get this postcard. You're collecting postcards, right? Aim for a full completion!
以上、グッズ告知でした！
That's all for the goods announcement!
はい、最後のお知らせです！船長とフブちゃんのネットラジオ「Vのすこんなオタ活なんだワ！」
Yes, the last announcement! Captain and Fubuz-chan's net radio 'V no Su-con na Otakatsu nan da wa!'
告知なんですわ！
I have an announcement!
本日8月11日配信の回にて、
In today's August 11th broadcast,
なんとサプライズで、
as a surprise,
船長の愛する『サクラ大戦』の
from 'Sakura Wars,' which the Captain loves,
李紅蘭役の
the voice of Li Kohran,
渕崎ゆり子様からメッセージをいただいてしまいました！
we received a message from Yuriko Fuchizaki-sama!
何やらフブちゃんがやってくれたらしくて、
It seems Fubuki-chan arranged it,
マリンちゃんにサプライズしようって。
to give me a surprise.
ありがと、フブちゃーん！
Thank you, Fubuki-chaaan!
ということで、超貴重な音源、
So, this super precious audio,
発狂する船長を聞けるのは1週間！
where you can hear me freaking out, is available for one week!
君たちもこの喜びをぜひとも聞いてください！
You guys should definitely listen to this joy as well!
以上、告知でした。
That's all for the announcement.
それでは22時の船長のプレミアム公開へ
Now, let's head to the Captain's
航海しましょう。
10 PM premiere.
出航ー！
Set sail!